Finding Aid for Barbara Bach papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Ann Arbor Community Service 1987-2008
  - Allen Creek Preschool
    - Board of Directors
      - Administrative Team Reports
        - 2004-2005 (Box 8)
        - Art Studio Proposal/Hanna Perkins Center 2005-2006 (Box 8)
        - Draft Budget Proposal 2006-2007 (Box 8)
      - Possible Relocation and Expansion Project 2005-2006 (Box 8)
      - New Premises "Expansion Project" Presentation 2005 (Box 8)
      - Finance Committee
        - Projections and Financial Review 2003-2004 (Box 8)
        - Communications 2004 (Box 8)
        - Communication 2005 (Box 8)
        - Duties and Reporting 2005 (Box 8)
        - Comments on Expansion 2005-2006 (Box 8)
        - Spring Recommendation to Close School 2006 (Box 8)
        - Audit Progress and Year-End Report 2006 (Box 8)
        - Review of 2007-2008 Budget, 2007 (Box 8)
      - Executive Committee (Box 9)
        - Meeting Minutes and Email 2005 (Box 9)
        - Founders' Resignations from Executive Committee 2005 (Box 9)
        - Email Discussion of "Governance Crisis," 2006 (Box 9)
        - First Executive Director 2006 (Box 9)
        - Treasurer Role/Possible Vacancy 2006 (Box 9)
        - Transition and Board Roles 2006-2007 (Box 9)
      - Nominating Committee 2005 (Box 9)
      - Marketing Committee 2006 (Box 9)
      - Finance and Development
        - Meetings and Reports 2004-2005 (Box 9)
        - 2005 Board Retreat, 2004-2005 (Box 9)
        - Finance Committee Recommendations 2006 (Box 9)
    - Fundraising Programs
      - Capital Campaign Background, Corporate and Individual Sponsorship 2002-2003 (Box 9)
      - "The Campaign for Kids" Capital Campaign 2001 (Box 9)
      - "Singin' in the Rain," 2002 (Box 9)
      - "Spring Spree," 2004 (Box 9)
      - "Do Well by Doing Good," 2005 (Box 9)
      - "Dining for Kids," 2006 (Box 9)
    - Resources on Nonprofit Governance and Fundraising, ca 2005 (Box 9)
    - Ann Arbor Area Community Foundation Grant Application 2006 (Box 9)
    - Operating Budget/Financials
      - 2005-2006 (Box 9)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 9)
    - Development Campaign 2006-2008
      - Overview, Budget, Board Retreat 2006 (Box 9)
      - Consultant/Coordinating Committee 2006 (Box 9)
      - Contact Instructions and Materials 2007 (Box 9)
  - University Musical Society (UMS)
    - Mission, Goals, Staff, By-Laws 2002 (Box 9)
    - Board of Directors Meeting/Year-End Financial Statements 2003 (Box 9)
    - Advisory Committee
      - 2000-2001 (Box 9)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 9)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 9)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 9)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 9)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 9)
    - Advisory Fundraising Ideas 2003 (Box 9)
    - Fundraising
      - Delicious Experiences Hosting 2003 (Box 9)
      - Ford Honors Program 2000-2002, 2006 (Box 9)
      - 2005 On the Road (OTR) with UMS
        - Notes and Email 2004-2005 (Box 9)
        - Budget 2004-2005 (Box 9)
        - Auction List 2005 (Box 9)
        - Promotion 2005 (Box 9)
        - Reports 2005 (Box 9)
        - Debrief Meeting and Thank You Letter 2005 (Box 9)
      - 2006 On the Road with UMS, 2005-2006 (Box 9)
    - Youth Education Program 2002-2005 (Box 9)
    - Education and Audience Development
      - 2001-2002 (Box 9)
      - 2003 (Box 9)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 9)
    - Hill Auditorium Re-opening after Renovation 2004 (Box 9)
    - Volunteering in the 21st Century 2008 (Box 9)
  - Performance Network
    (formerly Performance Network Theatre (PNT))
    - Gala Silent Auction Benefit
      - "All the World's a Stage," 2005, 2006 (Box 9)
      - 25th Anniversary Gala 2007 (Box 9)
      - "Pasta, Passion and Pistols," 2007 (Box 9)
      - Provincial France Theme 2008 (Box 9)
    - Staff
      - Executive Artistic Director/Artistic Director 2005-2007 (Box 9)
      - Executive Director (Interim) 2007 (Box 9)
      - Managing Director, Government Funding Moratorium 2007 (Box 9)
      - Development Director 2007 (Box 9)
      - Marketing Director 2007 (Box 9)
      - Job Descriptions 2007 (Box 9)
      - Evaluation Procedures 2007 (Box 9)
    - Executive Committee
      - Turnaround Plan Communications 2005-2007 (Box 9)
      - Development Plan 2006-2007 (Box 9)
      - Meeting Agendas and Email 2007 (Box 9)
    - Board President
      - Board Development and Fundraising
        - Nonprofit Governance 2004, 2005, 2006-2007 (Box 9)
        - Communications 2005-2008 (Box 9)
      - Michigan Council for Arts and Cultural Affairs (MCACA), Grant Application 2006 (Box 9)
      - Mementos
        - Local Newspaper Coverage 2003, 2005 undated (Box 9)
        - "Best Show," Sor Juana Ines de la Cruz 2003 (Box 9)
      - Special Report American Theatre, "Where Are We Now?" 2006 (Box 9)
    - Board of Directors (Box 10)
      - By-Laws 2005-2007 (Box 10)
      - Nominations and Director Profiles 2005, 2007 (Box 10)
      - Meeting Agendas 2006 (Box 10)
      - Meeting Agendas and Minutes 2007 (Box 10)
      - Organizational Development Training Materials 2007 (Box 10)
      - Centers for Excellence
        - Vision and Image 2007 (Box 10)
        - Consultant, Laurence N. Smith 2007 (Box 10)
        - Leadership "Champions," 2007 (Box 10)
        - Suggested 10/90s 2007 (Box 10)
        - Action Planning 2007 (Box 10)
      - Special Board Meeting
        - October, 2007 (Box 10)
        - November, 2007 (Box 10)
        - Draft of "Closure" Letter 2007 (Box 10)
    - Sustainability Initiative
      - Imagine Campaign Presentation 2006 (Box 10)
      - Cash Flow Situation Analysis 2007 (Box 10)
      - Goals and Procedure 2007 (Box 10)
    - Annual Budget Discussions
      - 2007 Budget, 2006-2007 (Box 10)
      - Cash Flow Management 2007 (Box 10)
      - Preliminary 2008 Budget, 2007 (Box 10)
    - Sponsorship Opportunities 2007-2008 (Box 10)
    - Playbills
      - Take Me Out, Christmas Carol, Moonglow, A Doll's House 2005-2006 (Box 10)
      - 25th Anniversary Season: The Fantastiks, Language lessons, Candida, Amadeus, La Traviata 2006-2007 (Box 10)
      - The Clean House, The Baker's Wife, Doubt 2007-2008 (Box 10)
      - President's Playbill Letter, The Baker's Wife 2007 (Box 10)
      - University of Michigan School of Music, Theatre and Dance, J.B. 2007 (Box 10)
      - The Village Theater at Cherry Hill, Inaugural Season Booklet 2004-2005 (Box 10)